// QUESTION & ANSWERS:
let question_array =
[
    {
        num : "1",
        question : "What do HTML stand for ?",
        answer : "Hyper Text Markup Language",
        options :
        [
            "Hyper Text Markup Language",
            "Hyper Text Pre-processor Language",
            "Hyper Text Multiple Language",
            "Hyper Tool Multi Language"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "2",
        question : "What do CSS stand for ?",
        answer : "Cascading Style Sheet",
        options :
        [
            "Common Style Sheet",
            "Colorful Style Sheet",
            "Computer Style Sheet",
            "Cascading Style Sheet"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "3",
        question : "What do PHP stand for ?",
        answer : "Hypertext Pre-processor",
        options :
        [
            "Hypertext Programming",
            "Hypertext Processor",
            "Hypertext Pre-processor",
            "Hometext Pre-processor"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "4",
        question : "What do SQL stand for ?",
        answer : "Structured Query Language",
        options :
        [
            "Stylish Question Language",
            "Structured Query Language",
            "Statement Query Language",
            "Style-sheet Query Language"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "5",
        question : "What do XML stand for ?",
        answer : "eXtensible Markup Language",
        options :
        [
            "eXtensible Markup Language",
            "eXtensible Mark Language",
            "eXtensible Multi-program Language",
            "eXtensible Multi Language"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "6",
        question : "Which of the following are Event Handler ?",
        answer : "Function",
        options :
        [
            "Interface",
            "Function",
            "Handler",
            "Event"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "7",
        question : "Who is a Father of 'HTML' ?",
        answer : "Tim Berners-Lee",
        options :
        [
            "Rasmus Lerdorf",
            "Brendan Eich",
            "Tim Berners-Lee",
            "Sergey Brin"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "8",
        question : "Which of the following is used to read an HTML page and render it ?",
        answer : "Web Browser",
        options :
        [
            "Web Server",
            "Web Network",
            "Web Matrix",
            "Web Browser"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "9",
        question : "What is DOM in HTML ?",
        answer : "Convention for representing and interacting with objects in html documents",
        options :
        [
            "Application programming interface",
            "Convention for representing and interacting with objects in html documents",
            "Language dependent application programming",
            "Hierarchy of objects in ASP.NET"
        ]
    },

    {
        num : "10",
        question : "What is the work of address tag element in HTML5 ?",
        answer : "Contains Contact Details for Author",
        options :
        [
            "Contains IP Address",
            "Contains Home Address",
            "Contains URL",
            "Contains Contact Details for Author"
        ]
    }
]